# Anna Sahaidachna

Address:

E-mail: anna.sahaidachna@gmail.com

Phone: +447599965272 Bristol, BS4 4FG

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a saxophone music teacher. I used to teach at Dnipro Academy of Music from 2017 to 2023 in Ukraine.

As a teacher, I have always tried to find a unique way for my students to keep them attentive and help them understand the complex topics of music theory. This role taught me to be patient with pupils who are struggling to learn or overcome barriers, and I take great care whilst helping them. Additionally, I was a member of the Academy Wind Orchestra. It helped me to understand the importance of teamwork and to take on more responsibilities like mastering my own skills that allowed the team to take on more challenges.

At the moment, since recent events in Ukraine, I found myself in the United Kingdom. I am open to new challenges and opportunities. I believe that my past experiences working with people will help me in finding a new role for myself.

#### **SKILLS**

Languages: Ukrainian: native, Russian: fluent, English: Upper-Intermediate

Open to learning

Organisational skills

Ability to work well with others

Flexibility

Responsibility

Leadership skills

Stress resistance

Ability to teach pupils

Digital skills (I can use a computer and the main software packages competently)

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Relocated to the UK

— November 2023

Music Teacher (Saxophone, Conducting)

Mikhail Glinka Dnipropetrovsk Academy of Music — Dnipro, Ukraine

September 2017 – June 2023

- Taught students to play the saxophone
- Taught academy students the art of conducting
- Timesheets; provided characteristics and references; recorded attendance and provided cohesive feedback on student's progress every term

- I took an active part in organising regional competitions among school and college students
- Took part in organising and conducting wind band concerts
- For 9 years I played saxophone in the wind band of the Academy of Music
- Played in Saxophone quartet for 9 years
- I was a curator for students of the wind department at the Academy of Music
- Monitored students' academic progress

# Music Teacher (Saxophone)

Dnipro Music School Nº12 — Dnipro, Ukraine September 2013 – June 2019

- Taught children to play the saxophone
- Recorded attendance and provided a cohesive feedback on student's progress every term
- Led the wind ensemble
- Prepared students for performances at academic concerts

#### **EDUCATION**

CODE Institute — Jun 2024 – Oct 2024

(Dublin, Ireland)

Junior Full Stack Software Developer

STEP Ukraine Employment and English Programme — Jan 2024 – Apr 2024

EnglishScore certificate — CEFR B2

Mikhail Glinka Dnipropetrovsk Academy of Music — Sep 2012 – Jun 2017 (Dnipro, Ukraine)

Became a Specialist in the field of study "Musical Art", speciality "Orchestral Wind and Percussion Instruments"

Achieved specialist diploma, equivalent to a Bachelor (Honours) degree in the United Kingdom.